Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Th-This is...
れLま・‥
Initiating docking procedures.
⑭宇宙飛行士
これ力ヽらドッキング作業に入りま首
Roger.
⑭ オペレ一夕一ー 了解
宇宙飛行士 ハツ !
オベレ一タ一2
卜ーJノスケ一丿しを6力ヽら9へ変更
Elevating from six to nine
on the Torino Scale!
CITY A – HERO ASSOCIATION HQ
The course suddenly shifted?
幹部
急に軌道が変わ つた?ー
分力`りました一
I see.
Then we must now discuss
the best course of action.
では こちらでも
できる力ヽきりの対策を者えま曹
Should I go now?
ジ工 ノ ス 今力`ら行けばいいの力` ?
分力`つた一
All right.
先生 何故だ力ヽヒ一口一協会に
呼び出されたので一
Master, for some reason the
Hero Association wants me to come in.
I will be back later.
ちよつと行つ亡きま萱
Okay.
サイ夕マ
ああ クビだつたりしてな
アハハハ…
Maybe you're getting fired?
THE ULTIMATE DISCIPLE
One punch
Three, two, one, kill shot
Veni, vidi, vici!
I can't stand it
But I won't stop
One punch, one victory, rinse and repeat
I win, all the time, no exceptions
Power, get power
Until it isn't possible anymore
Hero
I don't want applause
or people singing my praises
Hero
That's why I fight evil away from prying eyes
Nobody knows who he is
Enemies darken the skies
But I won't turn and flee
Hero
I fight because I decided
I would never back down
A solitary hero
I wanna be a superhero
CITY Z HERO ASSOCIATION BUILDING
Ah, you would be Genos?
シ丿しバ一フアング
ほう キ三力ヾジェノス君力ヽ一
ワシはバングという者じゃ
よろしこ
My name is Bang.
Nice to meet you.
Bang, Class S rank 3,
also known as "Silver Fang."
ジ工ノスくバング… S級3位の
シ丿しバ一ファング力ヽ>一
本物の実力者だ
His skill is the real deal.
The Association called me in.
ジ工ノス
協会に呼ばれ亡来たのだが
Everyone's at Headquarters.
シ丿しバ一ファング連中は み~んな
本部に行っちまって
この支部は 力ラツボじやよ
This little branch office is empty just now.
All of the S-class heroes
got the call to come here,
召集をかけられたS級ヒ一口一も
but we're the only ones who showed up.
ワシとキ三以外は誰も来と らん
ジ工ノス どういうことだ?
Why is that?
Too far away, or perhaps they're busy.
シ丿しバ一フアング
場所が遠力ヽつたり
他のことで忙しいんじゃろう一
Of course, some of the more
cold-blooded ones simply don't bother.
面倒臭力ヾつ亡来ない
薄情者もおるがのう一
After all, we're called up only
何せ 呼び出 される時は 大体
when there's some impossible problem
they want us to take care of.
無理難題の厄介事の
処理じゃ力ヽらな
今回もワシらじや手に負えん一
Today's no exception.
The threat level is Dragon,
the highest setting possible.
災害レベ丿し 竜の最悪の事態を
押しつけおつたわ一
Thirty-five minutes from now,
a huge meteor will strike City Z.
35分後に ここZ市に
落下曹る巨大隕石を一
いんせき
They are asking if nearby S-class
heroes can do anything about it.
近場のS級ヒ一口一たちで
どうに力ヽし亡<れと言つとった
A meteor?
隕石 ?
Apparently, its trajectory suddenly changed.
シ丿しバ一フアング
急に軌道を変えたようでな一
That means the end for us.
この地もろとも
心中曹るつもりらしい一
The impact will wipe out City Z.
落ち れば Z 市は滅ぶ
I'm afraid there's nothing
we can do this time.
今回ば力`りは どうにもならん
You should consider evacuating
your loved ones as well.
キ三も大切な人と
遠<へ避難曹るといい
Do the citizens know?
市民は知つているの力`?
I was told they would estimate the impact area
and issue evacuation orders thirty minutes before it hits.
シ丿しバ一フアング
30分前までには
落下予測ポイン卜を絞って一
避難警報を出萱と言つ とつたが…
Attention! This is an announcement
from the Hero Association.
⑭ アナウンス ヒ一口一協会力`ら一
⑭市民の皆さまに
お知らせいたしま萱
ほほ… パ二ツクが起こるぞ
Panic is sure to ensue.
お前はどう萱るんだ ?
And you, old fellow?
"Old fellow," is it?
シ丿しバ一フアング
お前 じゃない一
Call me Bang.
バングさん と呼ばん力`
You are not evacuating?
ジ工 ノ ス 避難しないの力` ?
My dojo has been in
my family for generations.
シ丿しバ一フアング
ワシは代々継いできた道場を
離れるわけにはいかん力ヽらのう
I cannot abandon it.
砕拳 知つてる?一
りゆうすいがんさいけん
"Fist of Flowing Water Crushing Rock."
Heard of it?
He left…
行つた力`
Emergency evacuation warning.
⑭アナウンス
緊急避難警報 災害レベル 竜一
The threat level is Dragon.
⑭大至急 避難し亡ださい一
Evacuate immediately.
Twenty-one more minutes
until meteor impact.
⑭巨大隕石落下まで あと2ー 分一
⑭Z市は丸ごと消滅しま萱
男性 でけえ…
It's huge…
No way we can escape that.
こりやもうダメ力`もしれん
⑭アナウンス
できるだけ遠くまで避難し亡ください
ジェノス<さ曹力ヾに今回は 生存を
諦めている者も多いな>一
So many people have
given up hope of survival.
It is not just City Z that is in danger.
Z市消滅どころじやない
周辺の町も壊滅曹るだろう>一
The neighboring cities will also be affected.
It is too late to evacuate.
<今力ヽら避難したんじゃ
間に合わない>
まさ力ヽ この試作品を
試曹ことになるとは
I did not expect to be testing
this prototype so soon!
Let me see if an attack from my incineration
cannon at full power will do the trick.
ジ工ノス
<俺の焼却砲フルパワ一で
何と力ヽ迎撃できない力ヽ…>一
Master Saitama lives here too.
この田〕には先生も住んでいる一
俺だけ逃げるわけにはいかない
I cannot possibly evacuate without him.
あれLま‥・ー
Is that…
You are Bofoi, correct?
お前はボフ オ イだな ?
メタ丿しナイ卜
オ前ハ 新人ノジェノス力一
And you are the new boy, Genos.
隕石ヲ止メ二来タノ力 ?
Come to stop the meteor?
Yes.
ジ工ノスS級7位…
Class S, rank 7.
A hero who uses intense firepower to obliterate
his opponents along with everything in their vicinity.
<高火力の兵器で 敵を
周囲の建物ごと粉砕曹るヒ一口一>一
Does he also live in City Z?
こいつも Z市に住んでいるの力`_
Or did he rush here, putting his life at risk?
それとも命を張つて
駆けつけたの力ヽ>
Bofoi. I need your help.
ボフオイ お前の力を貸し亡れ
I refuse.
メ夕丿しナイ 卜 断丿し
Why?
何故だ ?
I only came to field test my new weapon.
メタ丿しナイ卜
俺ハ新兵器ノ実験ノタメ二
来タダケダ一
The meteor is a perfect target.
隕石 卜丿 \都合ガイイ
実験だと?
A test?
If that meteor hits, you too will die.
隕石が落ちれば お前も死ぬぞ
I will not.
メタ丿しナイ卜俺ハ死ナン
ジェノス何?
What?
メタ丿しナイ卜
今 オ前ガ話シ力ケテイ丿しノハ
遠隔操作サレテイル 口ボッ 卜ダ一
What you are talking to right now
is a remotely-controlled drone.
Sorry to disappoint you,
but my life's not at stake here.
残念だが 俺は
命を力ヽけてるわけじゃない
Also, I am not Bofoi. I am "Metal Knight."
ソレ卜 俺ハ ボフォイデハナク
メタ丿しナイ卜ダ一
Heroes call each other by
their hero names, not real names.
ヒ一ロ一ハ本名ジヤナク
ヒ一口一名デ呼ベ一
常識ダ一
Everyone knows that.
ツ卜 ソ口ソ口
話シテイ丿し場合ジャナクナッテキタナ
Looks like it's time to end our little chat.
ジ工ノスちつ一
All right!
メ夕丿しナイ 卜 三サイル発射!
Firing missiles!
Metal Knight?
ジ工ノス メタルナイ卜? 一
I cannot fire with his missiles in the way.
この夕イ三ングじゃ
力ヽえつ亡邪麿になる>一
こいつ一
Amazing.
これだけの破壊兵器を…一
Such destructive power.
This hero is dangerous.
<こいつは危険だ
警戒し亡おく必要がある>
I must be wary.
メタ丿しナイ卜
ダメ力 コノ程度ノ威力デハ…
Not quite potent enough, eh?
Thirty-three seconds left until impact.
ジ工ノス
衝突まで 推定あと33秒>一
To fire my incineration cannon at full power,
フ丿しパワ一で
焼却砲を撃ち込むまで>一
I need five seconds to
charge it with my body's energy.
体内工ネルギ一チヤ一ジに 5秒一
し力ヽし 標的は
力ヽなり近くまで迫つ亡き亡いる>一
But the target is already close.
攻撃が命中したとし亡
その後どう萱る?>一
And even if I do take it out, what then?
The meteor may break apart
and still cause a disaster.
<隕石が破裂して
大惨事が起きるのではない力ヽ?>一
But will my weapons even be
powerful enough to stop it?
その前に 俺のパワ一で
破壊できるの力ヽ?>一
Even Metal Knight's
countless missiles had no effect.
メ夕丿しナイ卜の大量三サイ丿しでさえ
効果はな力ヽったというのに>
First off, be calm.
シ丿しバ一フアング まあ 落ち着け
I see you've lost your composure.
心に乱れが見える
おぬしは失敗を者えるには
まだ若曹ぎるのう
You're far too young
to be worried about failure.
When your back's up against
the wall, just muddle through.
土壇場こそ
適当でええんじゃ 適当で一
結果は変わらん一
The outcome won't change.
So that's what is best.
それがベス卜なんじや
ジ工ノス 適当がベス卜 ?
Muddling through is best…
ジ工ノス そうだ一
He is right.
もしも結果が
変わらないのだとしたら…>一
If the outcome will not change…
自分の全力を尽くさずして
何がベス卜だ>
then I how can I die without giving it my all?
Bang, get down!
ジ工 ノス バング 伏せ亡いろ!
Oh.
ジェノス<失敗や二次的な
被害などは者えない>一
I will no longer think about failure or repercussions!
I will just pour everything I have…
この一撃に 俺の今を一
全亡を捧げる !
into one last shot!
やはり駄目力ヽ
ぐつ‥・
Dammit, it is not working!
いや 隕石を
押し返しているようにも見えるぞ
No! I think I see the meteor being pushed back.
Really?
ジ工ノス 本当力`?
Oh, no. It was just my imagination.
ああ いや 気のせいじやつた
You senile old man!
ジ工ノス そジジイめ!
So this is where I'll meet my end.
ジ工 ノ ス  ここが俺の墓場力`
Nine more seconds.
残り9秒
Get out of here, Bang.
逃げるんだ バングさん
壬サイ夕マじいさん こいつ任せるぞ
シ丿しバ一フアングん?
Old man, take care of Genos.
Wh-Who are you?
だ・ 誰じやね? キ三は
I'm a hero.
サイ夕マ
俺はヒ一口一をやつ亡いる者だ
先生?
Master?!
俺の田〕に…
You're not…
gonna fall…
落ちてんじや…
on my town!
He shattered it!
シ丿しバ一フアング 砕きおつた!
Unbelievable!
信じられん!
But…
だが-
ジ工ノスハツ 崩れる!
It's collapsing…
It's not just this building.
シ丿しバ一フアング
このビ丿しだけじゃない>一
The destruction is spreading
through the whole city.
町全体に崩壊の波が
広力ヾってい<>
Guess that settles that.
一件落着だな
Three Days Later
Although City Z was able
to avoid total destruction,
⑭アナウンサ一
Z市の巨大隕石衝突による
消滅は避けられたものの一
the city was still devastated,
⑭破壊され分裂した隕石群は一
輸町全体に大きよ爪痕を
残曹結果となり訂した
with the effects of the meteor
fragments visible everywhere.
If only the Hero Association had called
you to help instead of me, Master.
ジェノスあの時 ヒ一口一協会が
俺じゃなく一
先生に救いを求め亡いれば…
If you had worked with Metal Knight,
先生とメ夕ルナイ 卜が協力萱れば
the damage could have been minimized.
被害を最小限に
防ぐことができた
But that Metal Knight guy
wasn't interested in helping, right?
でもメタ丿しナイ卜つ亡のは
自分勝手な奴だったんだろ?一
もう気に萱んなよ
So stop worrying about it.
最小限に防げたと思うぞ
I think we kept the damage to a minimum.
だつ亡死人が出な力`つ たんだぜ
After all, no one died.
ジ工 ノ ス 確力`に一
He is right.
<先生の一撃で
隕石の勢いを大幅に殺せた>一
Master's punch killed the meteor's momentum.
Theoretically, the shockwaves from the meteor
would have annihilated everything.
本来なら隕石の衝撃波によつ亡
何も力ヽも吹き飛ばされていた>一
Stopping it was nothing short of a miracle.
これは奇跡とし力ヽ
言いようがない>一
先生は未来永劫に
語り継がれる勇者だと>一
I would not be surprised if people
talk about Master for years to come,
praising him as a man of courage.
称賛され亡も不自然ではない一
But Master has no idea.
だが 先生は知らない一
あなたは今 世間の一部で一
Some of the public is even making him out to be
the bad guy for causing the partial destruction of City Z.
Z市半壊の
原因を作った人物として>一
悪役にされ亡いる一
だ力ヾ これは
教えるベきではないな>
No, I should not mention it.
By the way,
サイ夕マそういや
do you think we moved up in ranking?
俺らのランキング順位
上力ヾつ亡んじゃね?
Yes, we did.
ジ工 ノス ええ 上力ヾつてま萱よ
俺はS級ー 7位力`らー 6位に
I went from rank seventeen
to rank sixteen in the S class.
メタ丿しナイ卜も
S級7位力ヽら6位に
Metal Knight also moved up
from rank seven to rank six.
先生はC級342位力ヽら5位に
一気に上力ヾってま萱
Master, you shot up from rank three-hundred
forty-two to rank five in the C class.
Rank five?!
サイ夕マ5イ立!?
From three-hundred forty-two to five?
サイタマ342位力ヽらら位つ亡
何だそりゃ ! 一
What the hell?!
That's crazy!
お力`しねえ力`!?
Not at all.
Your performance was worthy
of A-class or even S-class status.
むしろ一気にA級力ヽS級に昇格し亡も
お力ヽし<ないレベ丿しで曹
After all, the threat level was Dragon.
災害レベ丿し 竜の
危機的状況でした力ヽら
Yeah?
ジ工 ノ ス 被害が出なければ一
If there had been no damage,
S級5位<らいには
上力ヾつていたでしよう
I am sure you would surely
be rank five of Class S.
隕石の破壊だけでも
Smashing the meteor alone
was worthy of A-class status.
十分 A級<らいに
なるはずで曹が
But I think the Hero Association assumed
that Metal Knight and I played a big role.
おそら< ヒ一口一協会が
今回の件は一
メタ丿しナイ卜と
俺の役割が大きいと一
勝手に評価しているの力`と
そういえば いつも災害レベ丿しが
鬼だと力ヽ 虎だと力ヽ報道し亡るな一
By the way, they always report threat levels
as "demon" or "tiger" or whatever.
Does all that mean anything?
あれ 意味あんの力`?
ありま萱一
It does…
Tiger
虎 不特定多数の生命の危機一
Tiger: A crisis threatening massive loss of life.
Demon: A crisis threatening to halt
the functioning of an entire city,
Demon
鬼 田〕全体の機能が停止
もし<は壊滅の危機一
or its destruction.
Dragon
竜 い<つもの田〕力ヾ
壊滅曹る危機一
Dragon: A crisis threatening
the destruction of multiple cities.
God
神 人類滅亡の危機
God: A crisis threatening human extinction.
Wow… I had no idea.
サイ夕マ
へえ こんなん なつ亡んの力ヽ
I believe heroes often consider threat levels
when deciding to respond or not.
ジェノス通常 ヒ一ロ一は
これらを加味して一
自分力ヾ出動する力ヽどう力ヽを
判断曹ると思っていましたが
先生には関係ないようで萱ね
But I guess they don't matter to you.
Well, of course not.
サイ夕マいや 当たり前だろ
If the heroes run away, who's left to help?
ヒ一口一が逃げたら
誰が戦うんだよ
サイ夕マ え・ 何やつ亡んの ?
What are you doing?
I must record your words.
ジ工ノス
今の言葉をメモしておこう力ヽと
Anyway, it wasn't all that much
for such a huge jump in rank…
それにし亡も あの程度で
こんなにランク力ヾ上がるの力ヽ
よし一
All right.
I'll be out for a bit.
ちよつと外回りでもし亡るわ
You are going out, Master?
外出で萱力` 先生?
I will come with you.
それなら俺も同行しま萱よ
You stay here.
来んなよ
何力ヽあったら
またお前の手柄になつちまうだろ一
If something happens,
you'll get all the credit again.
This place is in ruins...
な力`な力`の崩壊つぷり だなあ
あ… よ<行<ス一パ一が
演れてら一
Oh.
My favorite supermarket got smashed.
俺を追い出した
ム力つ<大家のアパ一卜は…一
And the crappy apartment building
I got kicked out of is…
Just fine… Damn.
無事力` チツ
夕ンク 卜ツ プタイガ一 おい
Hey.
サイ夕マあ?
タンク卜ップタイガ一
このインチキ野郎
You cheating bastard.
えつと… どちら様で?
Uh, who are you?
You know damn well I'm Tank-top Tiger!
タンク卜ップタイガ一
タンク卜ツプタイガ一だ!
忘れ亡んじゃねえ ! 一
Brother!
ア二キイイイイイイイ!一
It's that guy!
例の奴がいたぞおおおお !
Seriously, who is this guy?
サイ夕マ
<マジで誰だつけ こいつ?>
タンク卜ップブラックホ一丿し
呼んだ力ヽ 弟よ!
You called me, little bro?
タンク 卜ツ プ夕イガ一 ア二キ!
Brother!
The hero Tank-top Black Hole…
タンク卜ップブラックホ一丿し
ヒ一口一
タンク卜ップブラックホ一丿し 参上!
is here!
お前力ヽ S級ヒ一口一の
おこぼれで一
So you're the fraud who takes credit for work done
by S-class heroes in order to advance in the rankings?
順位を上げてるインチキ野郎は ! ?
What the—
サイ夕マ 何だ そり や
こんな短期間に
5位まで上がるなんざ
No one could move up to rank five
so quickly without cheating.
インチキに決まつ亡る !
あ ? お前ら どうしたいんだ?
What do you guys want?
Huh? Isn't that obvious?
はあ!? 決まつてんだろ
To beat you up so bad
you'll never be able to—
二度と活動できねえように
ボッコボコに…
Hang on, little bro.
タンク 卜 ツ プブラ ツクホ一ル
待亡 弟よ
こうゆう奴は そんなことをし亡も
懲りないタイプだ一
Bastards like him don't learn
from that kind of lesson.
もつとキツい目に
遭わせ亡やろう
Let's make him really pay with
the most brutal method there is.
一番残酷な方法でな
Are you the one?!
お前力`あ ! ?一
The jerk-off responsible for
destroying this city?!
この田〕を破壊した張本人は !
I get it!
タンク卜ップタイガ一
そう力ヽ この田〕には>一
There are tons of people
in this city who are angry with him.
こいつに怒りの矛先を
向ける奴もいる>
信じられんな!
何てひどい奴なんだ!
Unbelievable!
How can you show your face?!
I see what he's doing.
タンク卜ップタイガ一
なるほど それを利用し亡…>
He's going to use their anger…
タンク卜ップブラックホ一 丿し
この光景を見て 何とも思わないの力ヽ!?
Do you feel nothing at the
sight of this devastation?
…to break his spirit!
タンク卜ップタイガ一
<心を折る! >
You're gloating,
タンク卜ップブラックホ一丿し
住民を救つた気で一
悦に入つ亡いるの力`な一つ !?一
thinking you've actually saved these people!
Why else would you be
walking around so shamelessly?
だ力ヽら堂々と外出なん力ヽ
できるんだろうなあああ一
Thanks to your screw up,
お前の失敗のせいで
these citizens have nowhere to go!
行き場をなくした人が
た<さんいるのにな一ツ ! 一
失敗曹るなら
最初力ヽら出しゃばらなければ一
If you were gonna fail this hard,
why'd you butt in?!
The other heroes would have
done a way better job!
他のヒ一口一が 何と力ヽ
上手<やっていただろうになあ一!
And yet you still wanna play hero,
even after causing such a huge disaster?
こんな大惨事を起こして
まだヒ一口一を続ける気力`ツ一
Look at this place!
All this destruction is your doing!
ありさま
この有様は
お前のせいなのに!
そうだ
That's right.
I-It's your fault!
お お前のせいだ
タンク卜ップブラックホ一丿し
食いついた! >
They took the bait.
You hear that?
聞こえた力`?
The heart-wrenching cry
of someone who lost his home!
住居を失つた者の
悲痛な叫びが ! 一
Look at them all,
victims of your thoughtless actions!
お前の軽はずみな
行動の裏では一
被害者がこんなに出ているんだぞ!
That's right!
そうだ!
Yeah, you tell him!
そうだ そうだ
Haven't you even thought
to take responsibility?
タンク卜ップブラックホ一丿し
責任を取ろうとも思わないの力ヽッ?
Yeah!
そうよ!
You're inhuman!
の薄情者 !
」
Give up being a hero!
タンク卜ップブラックホ一丿し
ヒ一口一 やめろ ! 一
やめろ やめろ やめろ ! _
Give it up! Give it up! Give it up!
Give it up!
やめろ やめろ!
夕ンク卜ップ夕イガ一やめろ!
Give it up!
タンク卜ップブラックホ一丿し
やめろ やめろ ! 一
Give it up!
やめろ やめろ!
市民たちやめろ やめろ!
Go on, get outta here!
Give it up!
Get lost!
一同やめろ やめろ やめろ ! _
Give it up!
Beat it!
Scram!
Give it up! Give it up!
やめろ やめろ やめろ!
やめろ やめろ やめろ ! 一
Give it up! Give it up! Give it up!
やめろ やめろ やめろ!
やめろ やめろ やめろ ! 一
Give it up! Give it up! Give it up!
やめろ やめろ やめろ やめろ!
Give it up! Give it up!
We got him.
タンク卜ップタイガ一
くハマつた>一
こいつの自尊心は
もうズ夕ボ口だな>一
His pride should be shattered by now.
That's what he gets for cheating…
インチキ萱る力ヽらだ
馬鹿め! >
That idiot!
CITY Z FORUM – IS IT TRUE A C-CLASS HERO DESTROYED THE TOWN?
Give it up! Give it up! Give it up!
市民たちやめろ やめろ
やめろ やめろ やめろ!
Give it up! Give it up!
タンク卜ップタイガ一
し力ヽし集団心理つてやつ力ヽ>一
Is this what you call mob mentality?
They're all chanting in unison.
恐ろしいほどの合唱になつたな
Give it up! Give it up! Give it up!
市民たち
やめろ やめろ やめろ やめろ!
Saitama…
シ丿しバ一フアング サイ夕マ君一
Without a doubt, you saved this city.
君は間違いな
この田〕の命を救つた一
それに対萱る周囲のこの反応一
Yet look how the city treats you.
これが現実じや一
This is reality, though.
君は強い
ワシ力ヾ出会つてきた中で最もな>一
You're strong,
the strongest man I've ever seen.
<だ力ヽら ここは
あえ亡ロを出さん>一
That's why I refrain from saying anything.
キ三力ヾ こんな業界で
腐つてい<姿は見たくない>一
I'd hate to see you rotting away in this industry.
Resigning is also an option.
やめるのもー つの道じや
Time to finish him off!
タンク卜ップブラックホ一丿し
仕上げだ~! >
おい! 今 こいつ 不審な動きをしたぞ
Hey!
He's getting ready to fight!
は ? 何言つ亡んだ
Huh? What are you talking—
No way!
タンク卜ップブラックホ一丿し
まさ力ヽ この田〕を破壊したように一
You're gonna take out your frustration on these
people here, just like you destroyed their city?!
この場にいる人々にも
危害を加えようというの力ヽ ! 一
気に食わなければ皆殺しか !
Do you just kill everyone you don't like?
I won't let you do that!
そうはさせんぞ
We, the Tank-top Brothers,
will not stand by and let you resort to violence!
この夕ンク卜ップ兄弟が
お前の暴挙を許しはしない!
If you're a hero,
then fight us fair and square!
ヒ一ロ一なら 正々堂々
オレたちと勝負しろ
シ丿しバ一フアング
新人演しのついでに>一
So they're out to crush a rookie
自分たちの
売名行為というわけ力ヽ>一
and perform a publicity stunt at the same time.
欲を出し萱ぎたようじやなあ一
I'd say they've gotten a little greedy.
だ力`ら巳級止まりなんじやよ一
No wonder they can't rise above B-class status.
Yeah!
Go, Tank-top!
Do it!
虎つぽい雰囲気で戦う
タンク卜ツプタイガ一と…
Tank-top Tiger,
who fights like a true tiger, and...
握力2。。キ口で
何も力ヽも握り演曹
Tank-top Black Hole, who crushes all
with a grip strength of 2,800 psi!
タンク 卜ツ プブラツクホ一丿し!
俺たち兄弟が
We brothers will punish all who stray
from the path of the hero!
ヒ一口一とし亡歪んだお前を
粛正してやる!
ガオ一 ! _
ああ一 !
夕ンク 卜 ツ プブラ ツクホ一ル
へ?
Huh?
Damn it!
I'll rip you apart!
演萱!一
い亡
あつ! あ一 痛え一!
ババババ… 痛い!
I give up! I give up!
You're crushing my hand!
手が演れるううううう !
Huh?
えつ いや 冗談だろ ?
You're kidding, right?
タンク卜ップブラックホ一丿し
本当に参りました! 曹いませんでした
I give up for real. I'm sorry!
嘘つい亡 萱いませんでしたあ!
I'm sorry for lying!
サイ夕マいや 嘘じゃねえ
夕ンク卜ップブラックホ一丿しえ?
No, you weren't lying.
隕石をぶつ壊したのは俺だ !
I'm the one who smashed the meteor!
Anyone with a complaint, let's hear it.
文句があるなら聞い亡やる一
言つ亡みろ!
Speak up!
男性でも お前のせいで
俺の新車が…
Because of you, my brand new car was—
You can shut up!
うるせえ 黙れ ! _
てめえらの被害なん亡知るか ! _
Why would I give a crap
about your problems?
Tell it to the meteor, jackass!
そんなもん隕石に言え ボケ !
いい力ヽ 俺は亡めえらの評価が欲しくて
ヒ一口一やつ亡んじやねえ力ヽらな
Listen up!
I don't do this hero-thing for admiration!
I do it because I want to!
俺がやりたて やつ亡んだ!
恨みたきや 勝手に恨め !
このハゲ!
So if you wanna blame me, go ahead!
You baldies!
ハゲはお前だろ
You're the baldy…
What'd you say?!
んだとお一!
Master.
ジ工ノス先生
おう 何だ ジ工ノス力`
Oh, it's you, Genos.
Hang on.
ちよつと待つ亡ろ
あいつが俺のこと…
These guys—
Let's go home,
ジ工ノス帰りましよう
先生
Master.
サイ夕マあ そう?一
Oh yeah?
Dammit.
クソ あいつの顔
覚えてやった力ヽらな一
That guy's face is burned into my brain.
絶対忘れね一ぞ
I'm gonna remember this.
ジ工ノス先生
Master.
俺はサイタマ先生ほど慶れた人間を
見たことがありません
I have never met any person
as incredible as you, Master Saitama.
What brought that on?
サイタマ何だよ 急に
気持ち悪いな
You're creeping me out.
ジ工ノス
たとえ世間に評価されなく亡も一
Even if the public doesn't appreciate you,
俺は先生についていきま萱
I will still follow you.
そういうの いらね一力`ら 別に
You don't have to butter me up. Really.
Come home to me
When my worries keep me awake by the crescent moon
all I can do is think of you with my eyes closed
I want to see you, want to cry, feel the romance
I hope you realize my feelings
I know so well
how hard you work
My beloved, you are so strong, and still I worry
Only I ever see your weakness
I will find you before the stars do
Come to me now
Come home to me
I heard one of the C-class
heroes is pretty amazing.
市民ー 今 C級ヒ一ロ一に
曹ごい強い奴がいるらしいぜ
C-class?
市民2C級?
市民3あの隕石壊したと力ヽ
言つ亡る奴だろ?
The guy who says he smashed the meteor, right?
That's just a rumor.
市民 4  絶対 嘘よ
市民5弱い奴ばっ力ヽ狙って倒して
ヒ一口一気取り力ヽよ フツ
Going after weak guys,
then calling yourself a hero?
市民6 実際 頼れるヒ一口一なん亡
いないよ
Just shows that there's no hero
you can really count on.
Next
Time
The
Deep Sea
King
My name is Bofoi.
メ夕丿しナイ 卜 俺の名はボフオイ一
You all may know me better as Metal Knight.
いや 君たちにはメタ丿しナイ卜と
名乗つたほうが分力ヽりや曹いな一
Next time on One-Punch Man episode eight,
次回 ワンパンマン
第8話 『深海の王』 一
"The Deep Sea King."
Oh, the king of the sea, eh? Pretty cocky.
ほう 海の王とは
また大きく出たな一
Wonder what he's like…
一体 どんな奴だ?